I get more and more compliments on how pretty my face has become.
Really? It's increasing.
But that's good. That's information that not many fans know.
Yes, that's right. It's information that's out there.
I think I'm going to buy something to make my face shine.
I'm going to buy something shiny.
I don't know what shiny is.
Maybe it's shiny for the video.
To make a video?
I dream about it.
I'm not the type to control myself in dreams.
You can control yourself in your dreams?
I mean...
The kettle and the idol.
Well, here I am again today, Starlast's sugar-fed kettle man.
Let's call today's guest.
This is Mr. Idol.
The foot chime rang. I am Ayano Kubo, attendance number 14.
Pleased to meet you.
Now, Ms. Kokubo, you are here.
You have been a member of Ebichu for two years now, haven't you, Kokubo-san?
Yes, it has. It has been two years since I joined the group, and I was in the third year of junior high school when I joined,
Now I am in my second year of high school.
And you are in your second year of high school?
I am 16 years old now.
Sixteen?
But I joined the group when I was 14, and in the meantime, Mr. Sakurai and Ms. Nakamura joined the group, so I became an older sister again,
But I have become more mature in the eyes of my fans,
Do you get that? Do you say that to yourself?
Yes, I do.
Really?
My face really looks completely different from the face I had when I joined the group,
Do you think that changes with consciousness?
I wonder if it changes.
But even MIRU has been complimenting me more and more that my face has become so much prettier recently.
So you are getting more compliments. But it's good, isn't it? That's information even your fans don't know.
That's right. It's information that has never been released before.
MIRU-chan says that Kokubo-san has become cute.
As I mentioned earlier, it's only been two years since I joined the group, but the younger members have joined as well,
Have there been any changes in yourself?
Yes, I have. But I also joined with Cocona and Nonaka,
So the three of us became seniors in a year and a half,
We had to teach ourselves more and more things,
We also had to think a lot about how we should act as seniors,
I think I became a bit more of a senior.
I think I have become a bit more of a senior,
Aya and Mr. Nejo were working together,
If we go there, we will be in a position to play a central role among the younger members.
That's right. Cocona actually makes the formation for us,
There were also lessons for just the five of us,
The three of us would say, "Let's do it this way," and so on,
It was an opportunity for me to grow in many ways.
Yes, it was a great opportunity for us to grow. Cocona's mindset also changes quite a bit in such a situation.
In March, you held your first birthday concert,
You produced it yourself.
That's right. I even looked at the costumes on my own instagram,
I also look at instagram and think about who I should ask for the costumes.
From who to ask? Wow, isn't that a lot of fun?
It was a lot of fun.
I found an idol of my favorite lineage, and from there, I looked for a costume designer,
Did you get to that point?
I got to that point and actually asked them to make it for me.
It's really nice.
I just got the photo of the guy, and he's cute! I've seen her with various people.
Do you design your own?
I sent them photos of people in their lineage and what they looked like.
It was fun to see how you came up with the set list and the world view.
It was a lot of fun.
I had a free concert, a birthday party, and another concert,
I had to do all of them at the same time,
It was a lot of work, but it was fun.
It was bad.
I was surprised.
I was surprised. To be honest.
I guess it was a busy time.
But it was a lot of fun,
I was able to think about what I could do to make it better,
I was able to think a lot about what I could do to make it better, so it was a lot of fun.
So, today's guest is also Yuno-san. Please give my best regards.
Oh! Do you make it yourself?
Yes, I do. Not at all.
That's a bit new to you, isn't it?
I'd like to try it. I think there has probably been one in the past.
I think we've had this program in the past,
Mr. M. Nagaoka
Mr. Abeshan
Mr. Nao
Mr. Bartow
and Mr. Yuno
We sent this information courtesy of Mr. Hakki-Pepi.
Thank you very much.